<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knights-rubbish-heroes on Shine Right Blog</title>
    <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knights-rubbish-heroes on Shine Right Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Yu Chao (趙佑) © 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Keshia Erasia</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/keshia-erasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/keshia-erasia/</guid>
      <description>Lore Keshia Erasia was once the happiest eraser in the world. His owner Bobby had always placed him inside an exquisite aluminum box after using him. Though becoming smaller everyday, Keshia still enjoyed the time with Bob…until one day, Bob tripped on a crossbar and dropped his aluminum box on the sidewalk. The pain was enough for Bob to forget the aluminum box and left. Keshia thus became just another forsaken rubbish on the side walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Othox Codox</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/othox-codox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/othox-codox/</guid>
      <description>Lore Othox Codox was once a magic codex written by the famous sorcerer Bobbington. Unfortunately, Bobbington was executed because homosexuality wasn’t legal then. All Bobbington’s precious publications were torn and ripped, some burnt in the merciless flames. Othox, though merely ripped into shreds, called for the Blessings of Rabimouchinus and gained a wheel chair to aid him. He practiced the magic written inside him as he ran away from the murderers and gradually became one of the greatest magic codex in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Ranawato Plato</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/ranawato-plato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/ranawato-plato/</guid>
      <description>Lore Ranawato Plato was once the most beloved plate of a famous philosopher, Bobus. As bad luck would have it, Bobus committed suicide due to the pain of existence. Ranawato then became an unused plate on the shelf (aka. rubbish). Overwhelmed by sad emotions, Ranawato dreamed of her deceased owner every night…until one day, a handsome spoon came and introduced himself. Ranawato thus forgot her past owner and ran away with the spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/bross/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/bross/</guid>
      <description>Lore Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp;amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas were once the best selling mp3 players. However, smart phones became a thing and they were thrown into the recycle bin by their owner Bobs. They joined the local gang inside the bin and became the SS brothers (even though they had no genetic ties). The gang leader Big Brother had good relationship with the founder of Knights Rubbish, Keshia Erasia, so he referred the SS brothers to Keshia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - The Knights</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/the-knights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/the-knights/</guid>
      <description>Keshia Erasia
Wendy Floopy
Ranawato Plato
Othox Codox
Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp;amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas
Unreleased Knights Glaseos Cakeos
Lumie Candie
Schi Schnail
Waitie Changie
Socklataaz Sockrateez

Back to Knights Rubbish project page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Wendy Floopy</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/wendy-floopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/wendy-floopy/</guid>
      <description>Lore Wendy Floopy was once the 6th installation floppy disk of a famous operating system. However, then came CDs, USB drives, and well, cloud downloads as replacements of floppies, so her owner Bobates the Software Engineer tossed her in the recycling box without another glimpse. Bored, Wendy’s biggest interest became collecting CDs in the recycling box.

One day, Keshia Erasia, the founder of Knights Rubbish happened to pass by and fall in love with Wendy, but Wendy refused Keshia because he is ugly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>