<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shine Right Homepage</title>
    <link>https://casd82.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shine Right Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Yu Chao (趙佑) © 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 17:20:39 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://casd82.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Publish a Graphic Novel With Amazon KDP</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/self-publish-a-graphic-novel-with-amazon-kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 17:20:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/self-publish-a-graphic-novel-with-amazon-kdp/</guid>
      <description>I just self-published my very first graphic novel Inter-dimensional Time recently, using Amazon&amp;rsquo;s KDP (Kindle Direct Publish) platform. In this article, I am going to share my experience with Amazon KDP, and briefly go through the process of self-publishing.
Introduction Amazon KDP is arguably the cheapest and most convenient self-publishing service out there. It requires no service fee and lets you publish your book in both eBook and paperback formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Tuner App Using Audiokit</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/ios-tuner-app-using-audiokit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 12:23:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/ios-tuner-app-using-audiokit/</guid>
      <description>I made an iOS Tuner &amp;amp; Metronome App last couple of months due to boredom. Suffering from boredom again this month, I decided to write an article on how I implement it.

In this article, I will show:
 How to sample audio from the microphone using AudioKit. How to calculate the notes from raw frequencies (of the sampled audio).  
I will not delve into how I implement the views since the code is quite bulky and tedious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Game</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/quantum-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:02:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/quantum-game/</guid>
      <description>THIS GAME IS A PROTOTYPE. IT WAS IMPLEMENTED ONLY TO TEST OUT AND DEMONSTRATE THE CORE IDEA, SO MOST OF THE GRAPHICS AND GAME ASSETS ARE PLACEHOLDERS.
Play Online On Itch.io
Core Idea Quantum Game (yeah I know, what a bad title) is an action game which the players should switch between being an electron or a proton to overcome obstacles in the level.

Electron and proton have difference sets of abilities, and are attracted/repelled by different objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter-dimensional Time</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/inter-dimensional-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:01:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/inter-dimensional-time/</guid>
      <description>Purchase On Amazon Paperback
eBook
Sample Chapters Recipe ． Movies ． News ． Life Pro Tips ． Ads 1 ． Ads 2
Description O piteous soul, in such dull dimensions thou sinkest&amp;hellip;

Inter-dimensional Time is a cross dimensional pseudo-periodical published by Schineright Publishing Inc. in the great nation of the United States of Eurasia, Earth (Œ-137). It features all kinds of appealing topics such as pseudo-scientific discoveries, interstellar molecular politics, techno-tech-tock-technologies, post-post-post-modern art, litter-literature, muse-music, move-movies, ravel travel gravel information, wal&amp;rsquo; liki mou&amp;rsquo; dædou yåk&amp;rsquo;, determinant advertisement, and other crazy but indispensable stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudkolimaca Answer</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/sudkolimaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:23:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/sudkolimaca/</guid>
      <description>Did you do it correctly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuner &amp; Metronome</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/tuner-metronome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:51:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/tuner-metronome/</guid>
      <description>A minimal tuner &amp;amp; metronome app.
Download On App Store (iOS)
Description This is an extremely wonderful app that not only makes the world a better place but relieves the pain of existence.

How so?

It is proved in researches of various fields of science that good music could calm one&amp;rsquo;s soul and cheer up the depressed. Since good music require accurately tuned musical instruments and precisely calculated beats, a fine tuner and metronome are essential to the production of great music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight Rubbish</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/knights-rubbish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 15:38:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/knights-rubbish/</guid>
      <description>This is an extremely cool game in development, but I have nothing to show now. Come back later.
Release Date Will release an alpha version before 2019 summer. The completed version might never be released sadly. (Since I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough spare time, and life is so short.)
Platforms Windows, macOS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shineright Studio starts...again and again!</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/shineright-studio-starts-again-and-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/shineright-studio-starts-again-and-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world, again!

Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been moving my blog around different platforms quite a bit this year. Within only 8 months I&amp;rsquo;ve switched from Google&amp;rsquo;s Blogger to a self hosted Ghost blog on an AWS server, and now, I moved all my articles on my AWS server to this new blog, using Hugo static page generator, hosted on GitHub.

The reason why I switched to Hugo on GitHub is quite simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:58:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/articles/</guid>
      <description>This page includes all the articles published on this blog.
Posts September 2018
Self-Publish a Graphic Novel with Amazon KDP

August 2018
iOS Tuner App Using AudioKit

October 2017
Shineright Studio Starts&amp;hellip;again and again!
Customized 2D Following Camera in Godot
Camera Moving &amp;amp; Scene Scrolling in Metal Slug 3

September 2017
My Experience in Google Summer of Code 2017
GSoC 2017 Conclusion

August 2017
Animate Nodes Using SKAction in iOS Sprite Kit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recordable Launchpad</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/recordable-launchpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/recordable-launchpad/</guid>
      <description>A launchpad app with recordable slots.
Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Description A launchpad app with 25 recordable slots.

This is a project I made accidentally when I was testing out the microphone and in-app purchase feature of the Unity game engine as well as the admob SDK provided by Google.
Features  25 Recordable Slots. Beautiful Background. Well, kind of. Download for Free (with Ads).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This private policy is effective as at 2017.10.29.
About I am a game developing hobbyist from Taiwan who can&amp;rsquo;t live without making games. Shineright Studio is not a registered company anywhere in the world, so the legal rights and responsibilities of Shineright Studio are held by Yu Chao (趙佑), a natural person. To contact me, please email to chaoyu@link.cuhk.edu.hk.
About the Policy This policy describes how and why I collect, use, process and share information about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boots Cuts</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/boots-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/boots-cuts/</guid>
      <description>THIS GAME IS A PROTOTYPE. IT WAS IMPLEMENTED ONLY TO TEST OUT AND DEMONSTRATE THE CORE IDEA, SO MOST OF THE GRAPHICS, SOUNDTRACKS, AND OTHER GAME ASSETS ARE PLACEHOLDERS.
Screenshot (Demo Screenshot)
Download On Itch.io
(Platforms: macOS, Windows)
Core Idea Boots-Cuts is a beatbox rhythm game. Players could record their voices as drum beats and play music notes by pressing the keys (just like other rhythm games).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tall as the Sky</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/tall-as-the-sky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/tall-as-the-sky/</guid>
      <description>Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Dev Diary This game is created to attend a developer challenge held by a Taiwanese online forum. Participants of the challenge have to write articles about technology &amp;ndash; which I chose the Unity game engine as my topic &amp;ndash; daily for a 30 days streak. This game was made within the 30 days, and a daily diary had been kept during the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kQq</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/kqq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/kqq/</guid>
      <description>Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Description kQq is a physics puzzle game where player should Guide Lil&amp;rsquo; Neg &amp;ndash; the main character &amp;ndash; to the Worm Hole by placing positive, negative or neutral charges on each game levels. The game consists of unique original soundtracks and artworks.
Features  Original Background music. Experience TRUE LOVE. Well, just kidding. Foster your sympathy for the color-blinded. Boost your IQ, reduce your EQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:56:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Graphic Novels Inter-dimensional Time
Games kQq
Tall as the Sky
Knights Rubbish (In Development)
Apps Tuner &amp;amp; Metronome
Recordable Launchpad
Illustrations Doodles
Game Prototypes: Boots-Cuts
Quantum Game
Open Source Projects Below are the open source projects I&amp;rsquo;ve contributed to:
PowerUp iOS (Anita Borg Institute)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 23:32:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Yu Chao.
I make great stuff.
This is my website.
Education  BSc. Computer Science at CUHK. (2014-2015, 2019-2021 hopefully)
 HSNU. (2011-2014)
  Projects Some games, some mobile apps, some black and white artworks, a graphic novel, and my life. Link
Experience  Google Summer of Code 2017 (with Systers) The first couple decades of being alive.  Links LinkedIn
Instagram
Goodreads
Twitter
GitHub
YouTube
404 Page Not Found</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customized 2D Following Camera in Godot</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/customized-2d-following-camera-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 16:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/customized-2d-following-camera-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, I wrote an article about some camera moving schemes used in Metal Slug 3. In this article, I will show you how to actually implement such a camera.

I will be using the open source Godot Engine with GDScript since I believe any programmer with could understand GDScript quite easily, so let&amp;rsquo;s get started.

First, lets define some variables we&amp;rsquo;ll use later.
12345678910 # Scroll the screen (aka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Moving Scene Scrolling in Metal Slug 3</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/camera-moving-scene-scrolling-in-metal-slug-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 17:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/camera-moving-scene-scrolling-in-metal-slug-3/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started to work on my first 2D side scrolling platformer recently. However, before diving into designing my own game, I did some quick research on various topics about 2D platformers. One of them is camera controlling (aka. scene scrolling).

I find some interesting camera controlling technique used in the Metal Slug series, so I would like to share my observations and analysis of how and when to apply those camera controlling schemes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience in Google Summer of Code 2017</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/my-experience-in-google-summer-of-code-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 15:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/my-experience-in-google-summer-of-code-2017/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve already posted an article about Google Summer of Code 2017. However, the post is mainly about the project itself. For this article, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share my experience and thoughts for the whole GSoC period.
Google Summer of Code 2017 was an extremely exciting and rewarding experience for me. I was very lucky to be accepted by Systers (Anita Borg Institute) for working on the PowerUp-iOS project.

Before heading straight into the actual GSoC period, I would like to write briefly about why and how I applied for GSoC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC 2017 Conclusion</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 11:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-conclusion/</guid>
      <description>(This is an overview and conclusion for my summer internship (Google Summer of Code 2017) in Systers on the PowerUp-iOS project. The original article is posted on systers&amp;rsquo; Blogger. Here is the Link.)
Overview PowerUp is an educational mobile game app aiming at providing adolescent girls with reproductive health knowledge, empowering them with better self esteem, and teaching them conflict resolution skills in social life.

It is a choose-your-own-adventure game which the players have to navigate an avatar to engage in conversations of different scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animate Nodes Using SKAction in iOS Sprite Kit</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/animate-nodes-using-skaction-in-ios-sprite-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 22:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/animate-nodes-using-skaction-in-ios-sprite-kit/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Sprite Kit is a really well-designed and convenient framework for iOS game development. In this article, I will briefly introduce Sprite Kit Action (SKAction in short), which is the bread and butter for animating nodes in Sprite Kit.
The Basics In Sprite Kit, every node can run an SKAction by calling the run(_:) function. run(_:) takes an SKAction as its parameter, and will perform the action immediately after the call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Review of Godot Engine</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/a-brief-review-of-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 15:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/a-brief-review-of-godot/</guid>
      <description>After finishing 2 of my projects in Unity, I was planning to try out something different and hopefully, more suitable for me to use. I did a quick research on some modern cross platform game engines: Godot, Cocos2d-x, Atomic, Love2D, Phaser, and of course, Unreal. I finally decided to look more into Godot Engine. In this article, I will write briefly about the features, the special node-scene system, as well as the pros and cons of Godot Engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build &amp; Test Automation for Xcode Projects Using Travis CI</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/build-test-automation-for-xcode-projects-using-travis-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 18:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/build-test-automation-for-xcode-projects-using-travis-ci/</guid>
      <description>Testing your code is a vital process in app development, since it could reveal bugs and mistakes before the users actually use it. However, testing your app whenever you make a commit can be tedious and time-consuming. This is where Continuous Integration (CI) comes to rescue.
Continuous Integration Continuous Integration is the process of building and testing your app automatically, saving precious time for the developers. In this article, I will demonstrate how to integrate Travis CI to your XCode projects (to be specific, iOS/macOS/tvOS/watchOS projects) on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Database Singleton Class for iOS in Swift 3</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/sqlite-database-singleton-class-for-ios-in-swift-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 10:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/sqlite-database-singleton-class-for-ios-in-swift-3/</guid>
      <description>Writing code for database querying or updating can be tedious, error-prone, and hard to manage. Therefore, abstracting the database operations into a globally accessible model class may be a nice solution. In this article, I will show you how to write a singleton class which wraps the database operations. I will use FMDB (SQLite) with Swift 3 to demonstrate, but it is just about the same for every languages and frameworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC 2017 With Systers on PowerUp Project</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-with-systers-on-powerup-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-with-systers-on-powerup-project/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to participate in Google Summer of Code (GSoC) someday. Fortunately, this year, I got selected by Systers, an Anita Borg Institute community for a mobile game project &amp;ndash; PowerUp. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write about how I chose which project to contribute, how I wrote my proposal, and what is the PowerUp project about.
Selecting Organizations When selecting which organizations to contribute, I focus mostly on what am I capable of doing, what interests me the most, and which projects would enhance my portfolio for my dream career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Game Design - Book Review</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/the-art-of-game-design-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 12:37:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/the-art-of-game-design-book-review/</guid>
      <description>Finally finished reading the famous &amp;ldquo;The Art of Game Design: A Book of Lenses&amp;rdquo; by Jesse Schell. Jesse Schell is a professor at CMU ETC (which happens to be my dream graduate school :D) and an experienced game designer. Throughout the book, he often explains some abstract concepts by his actual experience in game designing (especially from the game Pirates of the Caribbean: Battle for Buccaneer Gold and Toontown Online which he designed) and performance art (he was a juggler during his teenage years).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D Fireworks Effect with Unity Particle System</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/2d-fireworks-effect-with-unity-particle-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 18:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/2d-fireworks-effect-with-unity-particle-system/</guid>
      <description>Using particle systems is a wonderful way to improve the juiciness as well as the aesthetics of your game.

When making my rhythm game Boots-Cuts, I used the particle system in Unity to display a little firework effect whenever a music note is hit on-beat.
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to make such an effect.
Texture and Material First, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to import the the graphics which we would like the particle systems to emit (aka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kQq: Mobile to Standalone</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/kqq-mobile-to-standalone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 22:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/kqq-mobile-to-standalone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve published my first game kQq on iOS App Store and Google Play in February. Though the sales were far from success, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot (or rather I like to use this excuse as self-consolation&amp;hellip;). Thinking that this game would also work on standalone platforms and that I would gain some precious experiences by porting the game to standalone platforms, I started working on the redesign of the project and published a Steam Greenlight page for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Budget Marketing for Indies</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/zero-budget-marketing-for-indies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 22:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/zero-budget-marketing-for-indies/</guid>
      <description>Marketing is an annoying and boring task&amp;hellip;at least for most of the indie game developers. However, you have to admit, marketing helps. It raises awareness among the potential audiences and possibly boosts the sales of your game.

The problem is, indies have limited budget, so it is impossible to practice the marketing skills which AAA companies use.

As I went through the process of developing and publishing my first mobile game &amp;ndash; kQq, I learned some basic marketing skills by reading tons of marketing articles as well as trying everything possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Game: Portrait or Landscape</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/mobile-game-portrait-or-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/mobile-game-portrait-or-landscape/</guid>
      <description>Modern mobile devices usually have a rectangular screen which one side is wider than the other. This results in a crucial design problem: which screen orientation is the best for mobile games?

This seems to be a rather simple and unimportant issue. However, whether the game is in portrait or in landscape could significantly influence the experience of the players.

Overall, to determine whether a portrait or landscape screen suits your game better, you should ask yourself these questions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Syncing in Rhythm Games</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/music-syncing-in-rhythm-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 23:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/music-syncing-in-rhythm-games/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started my beatbox rhythm game project Boots-Cut using Unity. When prototyping the basic game mechanics, I found that it is quite tricky to sync the music notes with the music correctly. However, there are very little articles on the web concerning this subject. So, I will try to point out some important tips when developing a rhythm game (especially in Unity) in this article.

Among all, I found the following three points with most importance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording and Playing Audio in Unity</title>
      <link>https://casd82.github.io/posts/recording-and-playing-audio-in-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 13:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://casd82.github.io/posts/recording-and-playing-audio-in-unity/</guid>
      <description>Just published my Recordable Launchpad app on the iOS App Store and Google Play! Actually, the project was created accidentally when I was testing out Unity In-App Purchase, Google Admob Unity SDK, the &amp;ldquo;Prepare iOS for Recording&amp;rdquo; checkbox, and Audio Latency.

Since integrating Unity In-App Purchase and Google Admob are rather straightforward, I would be writing mostly about (the more troublesome parts, which are)
 Serializing and Deserializing AudioClips Getting Rid of Audio Latency Prepare iOS for Recording and iPhoneSpeakerFix  in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>