<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shine Right Homepage</title>
    <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shine Right Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Yu Chao (趙佑) © 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project: YARC - Cloning Reddit Using Go and Vue</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/project-yarc-cloning-reddit-using-go-and-vue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 12:43:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/project-yarc-cloning-reddit-using-go-and-vue/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t get an internship this summer. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t because of COVID-19 or failing interviews, I simply didn&amp;rsquo;t apply to any. I felt that since I would be working something like 9-to-5 for the next 20, 30, or 40 years after I graduate, why would I spend my last summer vacation on&amp;hellip;working? So, instead of going through the anxiety of internship searching, I designed a few side projects and started working on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3100 Software Engineering - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3100/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3100/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2020 Spring
Remote Teaching due to COVID19
Instructor: Prof. Lyu Rung Tsong Michael
Grading Scheme  6 written assignments (20%) Group project - (free topic) web application (40%) Final exam (40%)  Midterm exam cancelled due to COVID-19
Textbook Fundamentals of Software Engineering. (Ghezzi, Jazayeri, Mandrioli)
Topics Covered  Software life cycle. Software qualities. Software engineering principles. Software specification: UML, DFD, FSM, petri-net, logic spec, ER-diagram. Software design: design patterns, step-wise refinement, TDN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3180 Principles of Programming Language - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3180/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3180/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2020 Spring
Remote Teaching due to COVID19
Instructor: Prof. Lee Ho Man Jimmy
Grading Scheme  Programming assignments x4 (60%) Final exam (40%)  Topics Covered  Names, bindings, scoping. Data types. Expressions and assignment statements. Statement-level control structures. Subprograms. Declarative programming languages: logic programming, functional programming.  
Covered in tutorials:
 COBOL Python: duck typing Perl: dynamic scoping Prolog ML  Textbook Concepts of Programming Languages. (Robert W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ELTU3014 English for Engineers II - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/eltu3014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/eltu3014/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2020 Spring
Remote Teaching due to COVID19
Grading Scheme  Resume writing (15%) Cover letter writing(20%) Business letter writing (25%) Mock individual interview (25%) Mock group interview (15%)  Review This is the third and final English requirement for engineering majors.

The first part of the course is resume writing and business writing. It was very easy and I don&amp;rsquo;t think the marking scheme is fair enough. The teacher required us to &amp;ldquo;elaborate&amp;rdquo; on every points beneath a listing, however, I believe most of the companies prefer short and concise bullet points to long elaborations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3170 Introduction to Database Systems - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3170/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3170/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2020 Spring
Remote Teaching due to COVID19
Instructor: Prof. Wong Man Hon
Grading Scheme  Final exam (30%) Programming project (30%) Assignments (30%) Short assignments (10%)  Midterm exam cancelled due to COVID-19
Textbook Database Management Systems. (Ramakrishnan, Gehrke)
Topics Covered  ER-diagram. Relational database schema design. Relational algebra. SQL. Schema refinement and normal forms. Database application development. Database storage and indexing. Relational operation cost analysis. Concurrency control and recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI4430/ESTR4120 Data Communication and Computer Networks - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci4430-estr4120/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci4430-estr4120/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2020 Spring
Remote Teaching due to COVID19
Instructor: Prof. Lee Pak Ching Patrick
Grading Scheme  Programming assignments x3 (60%) Final exam (40%)  For ESTR students, there are 5 programming assignments instead.
Textbook Computer Networking: A Top-Down Approach. (J. Kurose and K. W. Ross)
Topics Covered  Socket programming. Multi-threaded programming. Application layer: HTTP, FTP, DNS. Transport layer: UDP, TCP, RDT principles. Network layer: IP, DHCP, NAT, ICMP, VPN, NFQUEUE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Journey in Programming Languages</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/my-journey-in-programming-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:17:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/my-journey-in-programming-languages/</guid>
      <description>In this semester, I am taking a course called Principles of Programming Language. It introduced some interesting programming language concepts such as dynamic scoping, duck typing, functional programming, and logic programming. However, what I enjoyed most in the course is that I got a lot of chance to explore and compare drastically different languages. In a 13-week semester, we had to turn in assignments written in COBOL, C, Java, Python, Perl, Prolog, and ML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI2040 Introduction to Python - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci2040/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci2040/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor (Class A): Prof. John Lui Chi Shing
Grading Scheme  Programming Exercises (40%) Final Exam (60%)  Topics Covered  Python basics. Functional programming. Object-oriented programming. Regular expressions. Numpy, Scipy, Matplotlib.  Review I already know Python, I registered this course for a GPA boost. To be honest, I only attended one lecture, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know much about this course. The programming exercises were pretty easy though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3130 Formal Language and Automata Theory - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3130/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3130/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor: Prof. Chan Siu On
Grading Scheme Original Scheme:
 Homework (30%) Midterm Exam (30%) Final Exam (40%)  Scheme for 2019 Course Cancellation:
 Homework (50%) Midterm Exam (50%)  Textbook Introduction to the Theory of Computation, Michael Sipser, 3rd ed
Topics Covered  Finite Automata (DFA, NFA). Regular Expressions. Context-Free Grammar. Pushdown Automata. Pumping Lemma. LR(0) Parser. Church-Turing Thesis. Reductions. Decidability and Undecidability. NP-completeness. Cook-Levin Theorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3150/ESTR3102 Introduction to Operating Systems - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3150-estr3102/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3150-estr3102/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor: Prof. Shao Zili
Grading Scheme Original Scheme:
 Labs (5%) Programming Assignments (45%) Midterm Test (10%) ESTR Labs (15%) Final Exam (25%)  For non-ESTR students, Final Exam takes up 40%.

Scheme for 2019 Course Cancellation:
The final exam is changed to a programming assignment.
Textbook Operating Systems: Three Easy Pieces
Topics Covered  Basic Linux systems programming. System Calls. CPU Scheduling. Memory Management. Concurrency: Pthread, Semaphor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3160 Design and Analysis of Algorithms - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3160/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3160/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor: Prof. Tao Yufei
Grading Scheme Original Scheme:
 Quiz (18%) Midterm Exam (32%) Final Exam (50%)  Scheme for 2019 Course Cancellation:
 Quiz (23.8%) Midterm (76.2%)  Textbook Introduction to Algorithms, 3rd Edition. By Thomas H. Cormen, Charles E. Leiserson, Ronald L. Rivest, and Clifford Stein.
Topics Covered  Recursion. Divide and Conquer. Greedy Algorithms. Dynamic Programming. Graph Algorithms. Complexity Theory. NP-complete Problems. Approximation Algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3220 Algorithms for Bioinformatics - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3220/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor: Prof. Kevin Yip Yuk Lap
Grading Scheme Original Scheme:
 Assignments (45%) Ureply Quiz (5%) Midterm Exam (20%) Final Exam (30%)  Scheme for 2019 Course Cancellation:
 Assignments (54%) Ureply Quiz (6%) Midterm Exam (40%)  Topics Covered  Optimal sequence alignment. Heuristic sequence alignment (BLAST/FASTA). Short read alignment (Suffix Trie, BWT). Sequence assembly (de Bruijn graph). Sequence motif models, k-mer counting. Hidden Markov models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3230/ESTR3108 Fundamentals of Artificial Intelligence - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3230-estr3108/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3230-estr3108/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Fall
Instructor: Prof. Leung Kwong Sak
Grading Scheme Original Scheme:
 Written Assignments (12%) Prolog Programming Assignment (8%) Weka Data Mining Lab (5%) TensorFlow Neural Network Project (20%) Final Exam (55%)  Scheme for 2019 course cancellation:
 Written Assignments (21%) Prolog Programming Assignment (10.5%) TensorFlow Neural Network Project (21%) Term Paper (17.5%) ESTR Research Project (30%)  Textbook Artificial Intelligence A Modern Approach by Stuart Russell and Peter Norvig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proving NP-Completeness by Restriction</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/prove-np-complete-by-restriction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 21:29:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/prove-np-complete-by-restriction/</guid>
      <description>Proving NP-Completeness is a core topic in the studies of algorithms. For most of the algorithms textbooks, they show some complicated tricks which reduce a known NP-Complete problem to another problem, say Q, to prove that Q is NP-Complete. This works because if problem A reduces to problem B, then B is at least as difficult as A. And since A is NP-Complete, B is also NP-Complete.

However, many problem reduction methods are extremely subtle and often require some &amp;ldquo;divine instincts&amp;rdquo; to come up with in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music in Film Terminology</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/music-in-film-terminology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 09:23:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/music-in-film-terminology/</guid>
      <description>Just took an interesting gen-eds course Music in Film last semester. Though I publish mostly technical or game dev articles on this blog, I really enjoyed the materials in the course and I&amp;rsquo;d love to share the basics (that is, the terminology) of the course here. (Note we refer &amp;ldquo;music in film&amp;rdquo; as the score music of films rather than the sound effects.)
Tonality vs. Atonality Tonality is a principle which the music is composed to center around a tonic central.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Ng Machine Learning Course Review and Brief Notes</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/andrew-ng-machine-learning-course-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 10:02:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/andrew-ng-machine-learning-course-review/</guid>
      <description>Just completed the renowned Andrew Ng&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning course (on Coursera) these couple of days. Since many people are curious about this course, I will do a quick write up on how I think about this course and what I actually learned.
About the Instructor Andrew Ng is the co-founder of Google Brain and Coursera, and an adjunct professor at Stanford University. He was also a former vice president and chief scientist at Baidu working on large scale artificial intelligence projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out Medium</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/trying-out-medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 16:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/trying-out-medium/</guid>
      <description>Haven&amp;rsquo;t been writing articles for almost half a year because I got back to school this spring. It&amp;rsquo;s really difficult to handle both the course works and side projects (such as maintaining a blog) at the same time, and I&amp;rsquo;m starting to worry that I&amp;rsquo;ll have even less time writing after I graduate. The &amp;ldquo;harsh&amp;rdquo; reality and &amp;ldquo;tough&amp;rdquo; life often change our hobbies into more &amp;ldquo;entertainment&amp;rdquo; ones unlike writing or other creative activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI2100/ESTR2102 Data Structures - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci2100-estr2102/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci2100-estr2102/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Instructor (Class A): Prof. Irwin King Kuo Ching
Grading Scheme  Written Assignments (5%) Programming Assignments (20%) Written Midterm Exam (20%) Programming Midterm Exam (35%) Written Final Exam (20%)  Textbook Data Structures and Algorithm Analysis in C (2nd Edition), Mark Weiss, 1997.
Topics Covered  Big O, Omega, Theta Notation. Linked List. Stack. Queue. Tree: Binary Search Tree, AVL Tree, B-Tree, Trie. Heap. Hash: Separate Chaining, Linear/Quadratic Probing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI3250 &#43; CSCI3251 Computers and Society &#43; Engineering Practicum - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3250-csci3251/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/csci3250-csci3251/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Instructor: Prof. Chau Chuck Jee
Grading Scheme  Group Presentation (20%) Class Activities and Quiz Question Design (5%) Group Presentation Writeup (10%) Peer Evaluation (5%) Industry Visit Report x2 (20%) Reflection Article (15%) Final Quiz (10%) Project: Learning GitHub (15%)  Review This course was conducted in a &amp;ldquo;flipped classroom&amp;rdquo; fashion. In each lecture, about 4 groups (of 4 people each) gave presentations on various computer science topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/course-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/course-review/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all the courses I have taken during my unversity studies at CUHK (The Chinese University of Hong Kong). I&amp;rsquo;ve written reviews for some of them. Hope this could help out some fellow CUHKers. Shoot me an email if you have questions (or to request a review for a course).
Computer Science Major Requirements  ENGG2020/ESTR2104 Digital Logic and System CSCI1130 Introduction to Computing using Java CSCI2100/ESTR2102 Data Structures CSCI3100 Software Engineering CSCI3130 Formal Language and Automata Theory CSCI3150/ESTR3102 Introduction to Operating Systems CSCI3160 Design and Analysis of Algorithms CSCI3180 Principles of Programming Languages CSCI3250+CSCI3251 Computers &amp;amp; Society + Engineering Practicum  Computer Science Electives  CSCI2040 Introduction to Python CSCI3170 Introduction to Database Systems CSCI3220 Algorithms for Bioinformatics CSCI3230/ESTR3108 Fundamentals of Artificial Intelligence CSCI4430/ESTR4120 Data Communication and Computer Networks  General Education  GENA1112 Aspects of General Education GENA1113 Student-Oriented Teaching and Seminar UGFH1000 In Dialogue with Humanity UGFN1000 In Dialogue with Nature UGEA2230 Introduction to Transformation in Chinese History UGEB2440 Chemistry of Food and Drinks UGEC2007 Transitional Justice UGED2133 Music in Film  Engineering Requirements  CSCI1110/ESTR1002 Problem Solving by Programming ENGG1100 Introduction to Engineering Design  Physical Education  PHED1003 Squash PHED1017 Physical Conditioning  Computer Science Math &amp;amp; Science Requirements  MATH1510 Calculus for Engineers ENGG1410 Vector Calculus and Linear Algebra for Engineers PHYS1110 Physics for Engineers I ENGG2520/ESTR2006 Physics for Engineers II ENGG2440/ESTR2004 Discrete Mathematics ENGG2430/ESTR2002 Probability and Statistics for Engineers  Language Requirements  CHLT1100 University Chinese I CHLT1200 University Chinese II ELTU1001 Foundation English for University Studies ELTU2014 English for Engineers ELTU3014 English for Engineers II  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ELTU2014 English for Engineers I - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/eltu2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/eltu2014/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Grading Scheme  (Individual) Informative Presentation (25%) (Group) Technical Specification Writing (20%) (Group) Project Pitching Presentation (25%) (Group) Project Proposal (30%)  Review This is the second English requirement for engineering majors. Students were formed into groups of 4 or 5, and were asked to go through the process of
 Coming up an &amp;ldquo;innovative&amp;rdquo; product. Writing a technical specification document of the product. Giving an informative presentation on a technical detail of the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENGG2430/ESTR2002 Probability and Statistics for Engineers - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/engg2430-estr2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/engg2430-estr2002/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Instructor (Class A): Prof. Andrej Bogdanov
Grading Scheme  Tutorial Participation (+ ESTR Presentation) (12.5%) Quizzes (12.5%) Midterm Exam (25%) Final Exam (50%) Homework (0%)  Textbook Introduction to Probability (2nd edition), by Bertsekas and Tsitsiklis.
Topics Covered Probability:
 Probabilistic Model, Sets. Combinatorics. Conditional Probability, Independence. Discrete/Continuous Random Variables, PMF, PDF, CDF. Uniform, Bernoulli, Binomial, Geometric, Poisson, Exponential, Normal R.V. Bayes&amp;rsquo; Rule, Total Expectation Theorem, Total Law of Variance, Law of Iterated Expectation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGEB2440 Chemistry of Food and Drinks - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/ugeb2440/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/ugeb2440/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Instructor (Class B): Kendrew Kin Wah Mak
Grading Scheme  Short Writings x2 (10%) (English: 2000 words, Chinese: 3500 characters) Essay (40%) Final Exam (50%)  Topics Covered Food Constituents:
 Carbohydrates in Food. Protein, Peptide Bonds, Amino Acids, Collagen. Meat, Fish and Seafood in Dishes. Maillard Reaction. Fatty Acids, DHA.  Food Preservation:
 Drying, Salting, Fermenting, Smoking, Spicing. Kimchi. Alcohol Drinks: Wine, Whiskey. Cheese.  Traditional and Modern Food and Drinks:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGED2133 Music in Film - CUHK Course Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/uged2133/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/cuhk-course-review/uged2133/</guid>
      <description>Term Taken: 2019 Spring
Instructor: Prof. Brian C. Thompson
Grading Scheme  Online Discussion Participation (20%) Quiz (10%) Project (30%) Final Exam (40%)  Syllabus Terminology:
 Tonality / Atonality. Major / Minor. Consonance / Dissonance. Style Topics. Leitmotif. Timbre. Diegetic / Non-diegetic. Audio Dissolve. Synchronization. Counterpoint. Acousmêtre. Performance Scene. Sound Bridge. Montage &amp;amp; Fantasy Scene. Theremin.  Composers:
 Vangelis: Blade Runner. (Progressive Rock, Ambient, Film Noir, Bradbury Building, Orientalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish Released</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/knights-rubbish-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:40:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/knights-rubbish-released/</guid>
      <description>My second game project Knights Rubbish has released!

Originally I was just doing some experiments with Godot Engine and trying to implement the bare bones of a platformer, but then the project grew larger and larger as I combined it with other mechanics I was testing. After a year and couple of months, Knights Rubbish was born!
Real Photos as Game Graphics One of the coolest features in Knights Rubbish is that most of its graphics are made with processed photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Keshia Erasia</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/keshia-erasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/keshia-erasia/</guid>
      <description>Lore Keshia Erasia was once the happiest eraser in the world. His owner Bobby had always placed him inside an exquisite aluminum box after using him. Though becoming smaller everyday, Keshia still enjoyed the time with Bobby…until one day, Bobby tripped on a crossbar and dropped his aluminum box on the sidewalk. The pain was enough for Bobby to forget the aluminum box and left. Keshia thus became just another forsaken rubbish on the side walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Othox Codox</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/othox-codox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/othox-codox/</guid>
      <description>Lore Othox Codox was once a magic codex written by the famous sorcerer Bobbington. Unfortunately, Bobbington was executed because homosexuality wasn’t legal then. All Bobbington’s precious publications were torn and ripped, some burnt in the merciless flames. Othox, though almost ripped into shreds, called for the Blessings of Rabimouchinus and granted a wheel chair to aid him. He practiced the magic written inside him as he ran away from the murderers and gradually became one of the greatest magic codex in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Ranawato Plato</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/ranawato-plato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/ranawato-plato/</guid>
      <description>Lore Ranawato Plato was once the most beloved plate of a famous philosopher, Bobus. As bad luck would have it, Bobus committed suicide due to the pain of existence. Ranawato then became an unused plate on the shelf (aka. rubbish). Overwhelmed by sad emotions, Ranawato dreamed of her deceased owner every night…until one day, a handsome spoon came and introduced himself. Ranawato thus forgot her past owner and ran away with the spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/bross/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/bross/</guid>
      <description>Lore Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp;amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas were once the best selling mp3 players. However, smart phones became a thing and they were thrown into the recycle bin by their owner Bobs. They joined the local gang inside the bin and became the SS brothers (even though they had no genetic ties). The gang leader Big Brother had good relationship with the founder of Knights Rubbish, Keshia Erasia, so he referred the SS brothers to Keshia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - The Knights</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/the-knights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/the-knights/</guid>
      <description>Keshia Erasia
Wendy Floopy
Ranawato Plato
Othox Codox
Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp;amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas
Unreleased Knights Glaseos Cakeos
Lumie Candie
Schi Schnail
Waitie Changie
Socklataaz Sockrateez

Back to Knights Rubbish project page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish - Wendy Floopy</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/wendy-floopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish-heroes/wendy-floopy/</guid>
      <description>Lore Wendy Floopy was once the 6th installation floppy disk of a famous operating system. However, then came CDs, USB drives, and well, cloud downloads as replacements of floppies, so her owner Bobates the Software Engineer tossed her in the recycling box without another glimpse. Bored, Wendy’s biggest interest became collecting CDs in the recycling box.

One day, Keshia Erasia, the founder of Knights Rubbish happened to pass by and fall in love with Wendy, but Wendy refused Keshia because he is ugly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Publish a Graphic Novel With Amazon KDP</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/self-publish-a-graphic-novel-with-amazon-kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 17:20:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/self-publish-a-graphic-novel-with-amazon-kdp/</guid>
      <description>I just self-published my very first graphic novel Inter-dimensional Time recently, using Amazon&amp;rsquo;s KDP (Kindle Direct Publish) platform. In this article, I am going to share my experience with Amazon KDP, and briefly go through the process of self-publishing.
Introduction Amazon KDP is arguably the cheapest and most convenient self-publishing service out there. It requires no service fee and lets you publish your book in both eBook and paperback formats. The best part, as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned, is that the dimensions, paper material, cover art, and pricing are highly customizable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Tuner App Using Audiokit</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/ios-tuner-app-using-audiokit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 12:23:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/ios-tuner-app-using-audiokit/</guid>
      <description>I made an iOS Tuner &amp;amp; Metronome App last couple of months due to boredom. Suffering from boredom again this month, I decided to write an article on how I implement it.

In this article, I will show:
 How to sample audio from the microphone using AudioKit. How to calculate the notes from raw frequencies (of the sampled audio).  
I will not delve into how I implement the views since the code is quite bulky and tedious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Game</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/quantum-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:02:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/quantum-game/</guid>
      <description>THIS GAME IS A PROTOTYPE. IT WAS IMPLEMENTED ONLY TO TEST OUT AND DEMONSTRATE THE CORE IDEA, SO MOST OF THE GRAPHICS AND GAME ASSETS ARE PLACEHOLDERS.
Play Online On Itch.io
Core Idea Quantum Game (yeah I know, what a bad title) is an action game which the players should switch between being an electron or a proton to overcome obstacles in the level.

Electron and proton have difference sets of abilities, and are attracted/repelled by different objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter-dimensional Time</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/inter-dimensional-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:01:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/inter-dimensional-time/</guid>
      <description>Purchase On Amazon Paperback
eBook
Sample Chapters Recipe ． Movies ． News ． Life Pro Tips ． Ads 1 ． Ads 2
Description O piteous soul, in such dull dimensions thou sinkest&amp;hellip;

Inter-dimensional Time is a cross dimensional pseudo-periodical published by Schineright Publishing Inc. in the great nation of the United States of Eurasia, Earth (Œ-137). It features all kinds of appealing topics such as pseudo-scientific discoveries, interstellar molecular politics, techno-tech-tock-technologies, post-post-post-modern art, litter-literature, muse-music, move-movies, ravel travel gravel information, wal&amp;rsquo; liki mou&amp;rsquo; dædou yåk&amp;rsquo;, determinant advertisement, and other crazy but indispensable stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudkolimaca Answer</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/sudkolimaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:23:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/sudkolimaca/</guid>
      <description>Did you do it correctly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuner &amp; Music Training</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/tuner-music-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:51:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/tuner-music-training/</guid>
      <description>A minimalistic tuner &amp;amp; music training app.
Download On App Store (iOS)
Description This is an extremely wonderful app that not only makes the world a better place but relieves the pain of existence.

Why so?

Because this app includes:
 Tuner &amp;amp; Metronome. Sight Reading Training. Sight Singing Training. Interval Dictation Training. Chord Progression Dictation Training.  
Other information:
BEHOLD!!! This app fulfills your biggest childhood dream, that is, it creatively combines tuner, metronome and music training into A SINGLE app!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knights Rubbish</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 15:38:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/knights-rubbish/</guid>
      <description>Store Page Steam
Description A co-op platformer fighter game made with real photos, featuring our beloved character Keshia Erasia and his friends. They have risen from the rubbish and they seek for adventures. Exciting, eh?
The Knights Keshia Erasia
Wendy Floopy
Ranawato Plato
Othox Codox
Sirurueruerue Senyesuensuesue &amp;amp; Sugsesugsem Sosas

and more&amp;hellip;
Features  5 hilarious heroes to choose from. Local co-op arcade. Cool combo skills. 5 levels in total.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stirling&#39;s Formula - Approximation of n!</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/stirling-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/stirling-formula/</guid>
      <description>I.Introduction: The Coin Tossing Problem Whenever you have difficulty deciding something, for example, whether to attend the lectures of a course or not, the most common thing to do in this scenario is to toss a coin and see whether the heads or tails of the coin is facing up when they land. Assume that the coin you toss is uniform, meaning that the chance of the heads to land facing up is equal to the chance of the tails to land facing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shineright Studio starts...again and again!</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/shineright-studio-starts-again-and-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/shineright-studio-starts-again-and-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world, again!

Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been moving my blog around different platforms quite a bit this year. Within only 8 months I&amp;rsquo;ve switched from Google&amp;rsquo;s Blogger to a self hosted Ghost blog on an AWS server, and now, I moved all my articles on my AWS server to this new blog, using Hugo static page generator, hosted on GitHub.

The reason why I switched to Hugo on GitHub is quite simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:58:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/articles/</guid>
      <description>This page includes all the articles published on this blog.
Computer Science Proving NP-Completeness by Restriction
Web Dev Project: YARC - Cloning Reddit using Go and Vue
Game Dev Knights Rubbish Released
Customized 2D Following Camera in Godot
Camera Moving &amp;amp; Scene Scrolling in Metal Slug 3
A Brief Review of Godot Engine
2D Fireworks Effect with Unity Particle System
kQq: Mobile to Standalone
Zero Budget Marketing for Indies
Mobile Game: Portrait or Landscape</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Diving Apnea Training App</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/apnea-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/apnea-app/</guid>
      <description>An apnea training app for free divers.
Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Description Everybody loves free diving. It is a dope activity which gives you strength and power.

This app lets you customize your apnea training tables and test your breath holding duration.

This is a must-have app for free divers!!!
Features  Customizable training tables. Record training histories. Breath holding tests.  Source Code View On GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recordable Launchpad</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/recordable-launchpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/recordable-launchpad/</guid>
      <description>A launchpad app with recordable slots.
Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Description A launchpad app with 25 recordable slots.

This is a project I made accidentally when I was testing out the microphone and in-app purchase feature of the Unity game engine as well as the admob SDK provided by Google.
Features  25 Recordable Slots. Beautiful Background. Well, kind of. Download for Free (with Ads). That&amp;rsquo;s It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This private policy is effective as at 2017.10.29.
About I am a game developing hobbyist from Taiwan who can&amp;rsquo;t live without making games. Shineright Studio is not a registered company anywhere in the world, so the legal rights and responsibilities of Shineright Studio are held by Yu Chao (趙佑), a natural person. To contact me, please email to chaoyu@link.cuhk.edu.hk.
About the Policy This policy describes how and why I collect, use, process and share information about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boots Cuts</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/boots-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/boots-cuts/</guid>
      <description>THIS GAME IS A PROTOTYPE. IT WAS IMPLEMENTED ONLY TO TEST OUT AND DEMONSTRATE THE CORE IDEA, SO MOST OF THE GRAPHICS, SOUNDTRACKS, AND OTHER GAME ASSETS ARE PLACEHOLDERS.
Screenshot (Demo Screenshot)
Download On Itch.io
(Platforms: macOS, Windows)
Core Idea Boots-Cuts is a beatbox rhythm game. Players could record their voices as drum beats and play music notes by pressing the keys (just like other rhythm games).
Source Code View On GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tall as the Sky</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/tall-as-the-sky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/tall-as-the-sky/</guid>
      <description>Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Dev Diary This game is created to attend a developer challenge held by a Taiwanese online forum. Participants of the challenge have to write articles about technology &amp;ndash; which I chose the Unity game engine as my topic &amp;ndash; daily for a 30 days streak. This game was made within the 30 days, and a daily diary had been kept during the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kQq</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/kqq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:57:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/kqq/</guid>
      <description>Download On App Store (iOS)
Google Play (Android)
Description kQq is a physics puzzle game where player should Guide Lil&amp;rsquo; Neg &amp;ndash; the main character &amp;ndash; to the Worm Hole by placing positive, negative or neutral charges on each game levels. The game consists of unique original soundtracks and artworks.
Features  Original Background music. Experience TRUE LOVE. Well, just kidding. Foster your sympathy for the color-blinded. Boost your IQ, reduce your EQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:56:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Games Knights Rubbish
kQq
Apps Free Diving Apnea Training
Tuner &amp;amp; Music Training
Recordable Launchpad
Books Inter-dimensional Time
Artworks Doodles
Line Stickers
Web YARC
Game Prototypes / Trivial Games: Boots-Cuts
Tall as the Sky
Quantum Game
Open Source Projects Below are the open source projects I&amp;rsquo;ve contributed to:
PowerUp iOS (Anita Borg Institute)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 23:32:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Yu Chao (趙佑) from Taiwan.

I am a computer science undergraduate interested in application development (e.g. web/game/mobile dev), database systems, and distributed systems. I focused on taking software systems related courses during my undergraduate studies. This includes database systems, computer networks, parallel and distributed systems, cloud computing, and software engineering.

I kill time by reading novels and listening to music.

I murder time by drawing, writing, developing simple apps, and creating random stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customized 2D Following Camera in Godot</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/customized-2d-following-camera-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 16:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/customized-2d-following-camera-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, I wrote an article about some camera moving schemes used in Metal Slug 3. In this article, I will show you how to actually implement such a camera.

I will be using the open source Godot Engine with GDScript since I believe any programmer with could understand GDScript quite easily, so let&amp;rsquo;s get started.

First, let&amp;rsquo;s define some variables we&amp;rsquo;ll use later.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10  # Scroll the screen (aka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Moving Scene Scrolling in Metal Slug 3</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/camera-moving-scene-scrolling-in-metal-slug-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 17:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/camera-moving-scene-scrolling-in-metal-slug-3/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started to work on my first 2D side scrolling platformer recently. However, before diving into designing my own game, I did some quick research on various topics about 2D platformers. One of them is camera controlling (aka. scene scrolling).

I find some interesting camera controlling technique used in the Metal Slug series, so I would like to share my observations and analysis of how and when to apply those camera controlling schemes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience in Google Summer of Code 2017</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/my-experience-in-google-summer-of-code-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 15:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/my-experience-in-google-summer-of-code-2017/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve already posted an article about Google Summer of Code 2017. However, the post is mainly about the project itself. For this article, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share my experience and thoughts for the whole GSoC period.
 Google Summer of Code 2017 was an extremely exciting and rewarding experience for me. I was very lucky to be accepted by Systers (Anita Borg Institute) for working on the PowerUp-iOS project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC 2017 Conclusion</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 11:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-conclusion/</guid>
      <description>(This is an overview and conclusion for my summer internship (Google Summer of Code 2017) in Systers on the PowerUp-iOS project. The original article is posted on systers&amp;rsquo; Blogger. Here is the Link.)
Overview PowerUp is an educational mobile game app aiming at providing adolescent girls with reproductive health knowledge, empowering them with better self esteem, and teaching them conflict resolution skills in social life.

It is a choose-your-own-adventure game which the players have to navigate an avatar to engage in conversations of different scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animate Nodes Using SKAction in iOS Sprite Kit</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/animate-nodes-using-skaction-in-ios-sprite-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 22:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/animate-nodes-using-skaction-in-ios-sprite-kit/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Sprite Kit is a really well-designed and convenient framework for iOS game development. In this article, I will briefly introduce Sprite Kit Action (SKAction in short), which is the bread and butter for animating nodes in Sprite Kit.
The Basics In Sprite Kit, every node can run an SKAction by calling the run(_:) function. run(_:) takes an SKAction as its parameter, and will perform the action immediately after the call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Review of Godot Engine</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/a-brief-review-of-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 15:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/a-brief-review-of-godot/</guid>
      <description>After finishing 2 of my projects in Unity, I was planning to try out something different and hopefully, more suitable for me to use. I did a quick research on some modern cross platform game engines: Godot, Cocos2d-x, Atomic, Love2D, Phaser, and of course, Unreal. I finally decided to look more into Godot Engine. In this article, I will write briefly about the features, the special node-scene system, as well as the pros and cons of Godot Engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build &amp; Test Automation for Xcode Projects Using Travis CI</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/build-test-automation-for-xcode-projects-using-travis-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 18:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/build-test-automation-for-xcode-projects-using-travis-ci/</guid>
      <description>Testing your code is a vital process in app development, since it could reveal bugs and mistakes before the users actually use it. However, testing your app whenever you make a commit can be tedious and time-consuming. This is where Continuous Integration (CI) comes to rescue.
Continuous Integration Continuous Integration is the process of building and testing your app automatically, saving precious time for the developers. In this article, I will demonstrate how to integrate Travis CI to your XCode projects (to be specific, iOS/macOS/tvOS/watchOS projects) on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Database Singleton Class for iOS in Swift 3</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/sqlite-database-singleton-class-for-ios-in-swift-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 10:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/sqlite-database-singleton-class-for-ios-in-swift-3/</guid>
      <description>Writing code for database querying or updating can be tedious, error-prone, and hard to manage. Therefore, abstracting the database operations into a globally accessible model class may be a nice solution. In this article, I will show you how to write a singleton class which wraps the database operations. I will use FMDB (SQLite) with Swift 3 to demonstrate, but it is just about the same for every languages and frameworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC 2017 With Systers on PowerUp Project</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-with-systers-on-powerup-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 20:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/gsoc-2017-with-systers-on-powerup-project/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to participate in Google Summer of Code (GSoC) someday. Fortunately, this year, I got selected by Systers, an Anita Borg Institute community for a mobile game project &amp;ndash; PowerUp. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll write about how I chose which project to contribute, how I wrote my proposal, and what is the PowerUp project about.
Selecting Organizations When selecting which organizations to contribute, I focus mostly on what am I capable of doing, what interests me the most, and which projects would enhance my portfolio for my dream career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Game Design - Book Review</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/the-art-of-game-design-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 12:37:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/the-art-of-game-design-book-review/</guid>
      <description>中文版 (Chinese Version)

Finally finished reading the famous &amp;ldquo;The Art of Game Design: A Book of Lenses&amp;rdquo; by Jesse Schell. Jesse Schell is a professor at CMU ETC (which happens to be my dream graduate school :D) and an experienced game designer. Throughout the book, he often explains some abstract concepts by his actual experience in game designing (especially from the game Pirates of the Caribbean: Battle for Buccaneer Gold and Toontown Online which he designed) and performance art (he was a juggler during his teenage years).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D Fireworks Effect with Unity Particle System</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/2d-fireworks-effect-with-unity-particle-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 18:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/2d-fireworks-effect-with-unity-particle-system/</guid>
      <description>Using particle systems is a wonderful way to improve the juiciness as well as the aesthetics of your game.

When making my rhythm game Boots-Cuts, I used the particle system in Unity to display a little firework effect whenever a music note is hit on-beat.
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to make such an effect.
Texture and Material First, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to import the the graphics which we would like the particle systems to emit (aka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kQq: Mobile to Standalone</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/kqq-mobile-to-standalone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 22:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/kqq-mobile-to-standalone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve published my first game kQq on iOS App Store and Google Play in February. Though the sales were far from success, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot (or rather I like to use this excuse as self-consolation&amp;hellip;). Thinking that this game would also work on standalone platforms and that I would gain some precious experiences by porting the game to standalone platforms, I started working on the redesign of the project and published a Steam Greenlight page for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Budget Marketing for Indies</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/zero-budget-marketing-for-indies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 22:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/zero-budget-marketing-for-indies/</guid>
      <description>Marketing is an annoying and boring task&amp;hellip;at least for most of the indie game developers. However, you have to admit, marketing helps. It raises awareness among the potential audiences and possibly boosts the sales of your game.

The problem is, indies have limited budget, so it is impossible to practice the marketing skills which AAA companies use.

As I went through the process of developing and publishing my first mobile game &amp;ndash; kQq, I learned some basic marketing skills by reading tons of marketing articles as well as trying everything possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Game: Portrait or Landscape</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/mobile-game-portrait-or-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/mobile-game-portrait-or-landscape/</guid>
      <description>Modern mobile devices usually have a rectangular screen which one side is wider than the other. This results in a crucial design problem: which screen orientation is the best for mobile games?

This seems to be a rather simple and unimportant issue. However, whether the game is in portrait or in landscape could significantly influence the experience of the players.

Overall, to determine whether a portrait or landscape screen suits your game better, you should ask yourself these questions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Syncing in Rhythm Games</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/music-syncing-in-rhythm-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 23:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/music-syncing-in-rhythm-games/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started my beatbox rhythm game project Boots-Cut using Unity. When prototyping the basic game mechanics, I found that it is quite tricky to sync the music notes with the music correctly. However, there are very little articles on the web concerning this subject. So, I will try to point out some important tips when developing a rhythm game (especially in Unity) in this article.

Among all, I found the following three points with most importance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording and Playing Audio in Unity</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/recording-and-playing-audio-in-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 13:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/posts/recording-and-playing-audio-in-unity/</guid>
      <description>Just published my Recordable Launchpad app on the iOS App Store and Google Play! Actually, the project was created accidentally when I was testing out Unity In-App Purchase, Google Admob Unity SDK, the &amp;ldquo;Prepare iOS for Recording&amp;rdquo; checkbox, and Audio Latency.

Since integrating Unity In-App Purchase and Google Admob are rather straightforward, I would be writing mostly about (the more troublesome parts, which are)
 Serializing and Deserializing AudioClips Getting Rid of Audio Latency Prepare iOS for Recording and iPhoneSpeakerFix  in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sashimi Sweets Hiring Elite 烏魚子公司 精英招募</title>
      <link>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/sashimi-sweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 1995 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://YuChaoGithub.github.io/sashimi-sweets/</guid>
      <description>Click this link to apply 點此連結申請</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>